(this["webpackJsonpmisha-react-genesis-game"]=this["webpackJsonpmisha-react-genesis-game"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,,function(e,t,r){e.exports={testBlock:"testPage_testBlock__2HFwS",moneyBlock:"testPage_moneyBlock__3sVUb",question:"testPage_question__1YCr_",answer:"testPage_answer__13R9s",answerWrap:"testPage_answerWrap__1kurZ",answerCorrect:"testPage_answerCorrect__1pe2H",answerWrapCorrect:"testPage_answerWrapCorrect__3nR4-",answerUnCorrect:"testPage_answerUnCorrect__2F3Gu",answerWrapUnCorrect:"testPage_answerWrapUnCorrect__M2ble",answerBlock:"testPage_answerBlock__2tv2t",auto:"testPage_auto__3Q8Cj",menu:"testPage_menu__3n5cn",none:"testPage_none__1MbZ6"}},,,,,,,function(e,t,r){e.exports={money:"moneyBlock_money__2upSX",moneyCurrent:"moneyBlock_moneyCurrent__3c_Rb",moneyPassed:"moneyBlock_moneyPassed__D0xTH",moneyWrap:"moneyBlock_moneyWrap__35VLf",moneyWrapCurrent:"moneyBlock_moneyWrapCurrent__3HJz-"}},function(e,t,r){e.exports={text:"finalPage_text__3U5hv",App:"finalPage_App__1_Bnp",textTotal:"finalPage_textTotal__2fBrr",img:"finalPage_img__2Dshz",btn:"finalPage_btn__17GId"}},,function(e,t,r){e.exports={text:"startPage_text__3_OVu",App:"startPage_App__1d8Gg",img:"startPage_img__3jq1U",btn:"startPage_btn__1VcYb"}},,,,,,,function(e,t,r){e.exports={button:"orangeButton_button__2MBqj"}},,function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"a":[{"id":0,"question":"In which modern-day country was the physicist and chemist Marie Curie born?","answers":[{"answer":"Poland","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Spain","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Ukraine","letter":"C"},{"answer":"USA","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Poland"},{"id":1,"question":"How many wings does a mosquito have?","answers":[{"answer":"One","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Four","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Two","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Six","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Two"},{"id":2,"question":"Which is the largest internal organ in the human body?","answers":[{"answer":"Finger","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Head","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Lung","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Liver","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Liver"},{"id":3,"question":"Arachnophobia is the fear of what?","answers":[{"answer":"Dolphins","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Cats","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Spiders","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Bees","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Spiders"},{"id":4,"question":"What is the collective name for a group of crows?","answers":[{"answer":"A murder","letter":"A"},{"answer":"A crows","letter":"B"},{"answer":"A birds","letter":"C"},{"answer":"A sparrows","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"A murder"},{"id":5,"question":"What part of a human body is the Mandible?","answers":[{"answer":"Bigger jawbone","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Lower jawbone","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Small jawbone","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Big jawbone","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Lower jawbone"},{"id":6,"question":"The rate at which the body produces energy from nutrients is controlled by which gland in the neck?","answers":[{"answer":"Carotid","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Neck gland","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Eyes","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Thyroid gland","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Thyroid gland"},{"id":7,"question":"At what speed does light travel?","answers":[{"answer":"185,000 miles per second","letter":"A"},{"answer":"204,000 miles per second","letter":"B"},{"answer":"160,000 miles per second","letter":"C"},{"answer":"186,000 miles per second","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"186,000 miles per second"},{"id":8,"question":"What is the largest moon of Saturn called?","answers":[{"answer":"Titan","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Ganymede","letter":"B"},{"answer":"Rhea","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Enceladus","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Titan"},{"id":9,"question":"Percy Spencer invented which time saving kitchen appliance?","answers":[{"answer":"The kitchen knife","letter":"A"},{"answer":"The Microwave cooker","letter":"B"},{"answer":"The cookstove","letter":"C"},{"answer":"He did not invent anything like that","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"The Microwave cooker"},{"id":10,"question":"Ascorbic acid is a form of which vitamin?","answers":[{"answer":"D3","letter":"A"},{"answer":"B12","letter":"B"},{"answer":"C","letter":"C"},{"answer":"A","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"C"},{"id":11,"question":"How many hearts do octopuses have?","answers":[{"answer":"Ten","letter":"A"},{"answer":"Three","letter":"B"},{"answer":"One","letter":"C"},{"answer":"Five","letter":"D"}],"correctAnswer":"Three"}]}')},function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"a":[{"id":0,"cash":"$500","cashNumber":500},{"id":1,"cash":"$1,000","cashNumber":1000},{"id":2,"cash":"$2,000","cashNumber":2000},{"id":3,"cash":"$4,000","cashNumber":4000},{"id":4,"cash":"$8,000","cashNumber":8000},{"id":5,"cash":"$16,000","cashNumber":16000},{"id":6,"cash":"$32,000","cashNumber":32000},{"id":7,"cash":"$64,000","cashNumber":64000},{"id":8,"cash":"$125,000","cashNumber":125000},{"id":9,"cash":"$250,000","cashNumber":250000},{"id":10,"cash":"$500,000","cashNumber":500000},{"id":11,"cash":"$1,000,000","cashNumber":1000000}]}')},,,,,,function(e,t,r){},function(e,t,r){},,,,,,function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(1),a=r(0),s=r.n(a),c=r(20),o=r.n(c),i=(r(30),function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,38)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,n=t.getFID,a=t.getFCP,s=t.getLCP,c=t.getTTFB;r(e),n(e),a(e),s(e),c(e)}))}),l=r(8),d=s.a.createContext({}),u=s.a.createContext({}),h=s.a.createContext({}),w=s.a.createContext({}),b=(r(31),r.p+"static/media/hand.dbb74bc4.svg"),j=r(21),m=r.n(j),p=r(10),_=function(e){var t=e.textButton,r=e.urlButton;return Object(n.jsx)(p.b,{className:m.a.button,to:r,children:t})},x=r(14),g=r.n(x),O=function(){return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:g.a.App,children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:g.a.img,children:Object(n.jsx)("img",{src:b,alt:"Hand with stars"})}),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{className:g.a.text,children:"Who wants to be a\xa0millionaire?"}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:g.a.btn,children:Object(n.jsx)(_,{textButton:"Start",urlButton:"/test"})})]})]})},f=r(4),v=r.n(f),C=r(11),y=r.n(C),B=function(e){var t=e.currentStep,r=e.id,a=e.cash;return Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:t===r?y.a.moneyWrapCurrent:y.a.moneyWrap,children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:t===r?y.a.moneyCurrent:t>r?y.a.moneyPassed:y.a.money,children:a})})},A=r(2),P=r.p+"static/media/Menu.2e4db3a9.svg",N=r.p+"static/media/Close.67d0a39e.svg",S=function(e){var t=e.data,r=e.currentStep,s=e.currentStepSet,c=e.money,o=e.redirect,i=e.redirectSet,d=e.cash,u=e.cashSet,h=Object(a.useState)(""),w=Object(l.a)(h,2),b=w[0],j=w[1],m=Object(a.useState)(""),p=Object(l.a)(m,2),_=p[0],x=p[1],g=Object(a.useState)(!1),O=Object(l.a)(g,2),f=O[0],C=O[1],y=function(e){"uncorrect"===e?(j("uncorrect"),setTimeout((function(){i(!0),j("")}),1e3)):"correctUnique"===e?(j("correct"),u(d+c[r].cashNumber),setTimeout((function(){i(!0),j("")}),1e3)):(j("correct"),u(d+c[r].cashNumber),setTimeout((function(){s(r+1),j("")}),1e3))};return o?(s(0),Object(n.jsx)(A.a,{to:"/finalPage"})):Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:v.a.testBlock,children:[document.body.offsetWidth<=500&&Object(n.jsx)("img",{className:v.a.menu,onClick:function(){return C(!f)},src:f?N:P,alt:"menu"}),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{style:document.body.offsetWidth<=500&&f?{display:"none"}:{display:"block"},children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{className:v.a.question,children:t[r].question}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:v.a.answerBlock,children:t[r].answers.map((function(e){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:v.a.auto,children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:_===e.letter?"correct"===b?v.a.answerWrapCorrect:"uncorrect"===b?v.a.answerWrapUnCorrect:v.a.answerWrap:v.a.answerWrap,children:Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:_===e.letter?"correct"===b?v.a.answerCorrect:"uncorrect"===b?v.a.answerUnCorrect:v.a.answer:v.a.answer,onClick:function(){x(e.letter),e.answer===t[r].correctAnswer?y(11===r?"correctUnique":"correct"):y("uncorrect")},children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{style:{color:"#FF8B37",paddingRight:8,cursor:"pointer"},children:e.letter}),e.answer]},e.letter)})},e.letter)}))})]}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:document.body.offsetWidth<=500?f?v.a.moneyBlock:v.a.none:v.a.moneyBlock,children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:c.map((function(e){return Object(n.jsx)(B,{id:e.id,cash:e.cash,currentStep:r},e.id)})).reverse()})})]})},k=r(23),W=r(24),T=function(){var e=Object(a.useContext)(d),t=Object(a.useContext)(u),r=Object(a.useContext)(h),s=Object(a.useContext)(w),c=Object(a.useState)(!1),o=Object(l.a)(c,2),i=o[0],b=o[1];return Object(n.jsx)(S,{currentStep:e,currentStepSet:t,cash:r,cashSet:s,data:k.a,money:W.a,redirectSet:b,redirect:i})},q=r(12),D=r.n(q),U=function(e){var t=e.cashWin,r=e.cashWinSet;return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:D.a.App,children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:D.a.img,children:Object(n.jsx)("img",{src:b,alt:"Hand with stars"})}),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{className:D.a.textTotal,children:"Total score:"}),Object(n.jsxs)("p",{className:D.a.text,children:["$",t," earned"]}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{onClick:function(){return r(0)},className:D.a.btn,children:Object(n.jsx)(_,{textButton:"Try again",urlButton:"/test"})})]})]})},$=function(){var e=Object(a.useContext)(h),t=Object(a.useContext)(w);return Object(n.jsx)(U,{cashWin:e,cashWinSet:t})},F=function(){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:"error"})},H=function(){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:Object(n.jsxs)(A.d,{children:[Object(n.jsx)(A.b,{exact:!0,path:"/startPage",component:O}),Object(n.jsx)(A.b,{exact:!0,path:"/test",component:T}),Object(n.jsx)(A.b,{exact:!0,path:"/finalPage",component:$}),Object(n.jsx)(A.b,{exact:!0,path:"/",render:function(){return Object(n.jsx)(A.a,{to:"/startPage"})}}),Object(n.jsx)(A.b,{path:"*",component:F})]})})},M=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(0),t=Object(l.a)(e,2),r=t[0],s=t[1],c=Object(a.useState)(0),o=Object(l.a)(c,2),i=o[0],b=o[1];return Object(n.jsx)(d.Provider,{value:r,children:Object(n.jsx)(u.Provider,{value:s,children:Object(n.jsx)(h.Provider,{value:i,children:Object(n.jsx)(w.Provider,{value:b,children:Object(n.jsx)(p.a,{basename:"/misha-react-genesis-game",children:Object(n.jsx)(H,{})})})})})})};o.a.render(Object(n.jsx)(s.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(n.jsx)(M,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),i()}],[[37,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.50be97f6.chunk.js.map